to low, double-digit growth range.
So that's been positive overall, I think.
But there's no question it won't get back to the really high growth rates
we saw a few years ago.
We also see a higher number of competitors entering in each segment as well,
which is something we have to just be ready for when we do launch in China.
Nonetheless, very large market, highly attractive,
and I think you've seen the strong performance that we've had.
You know, I think for Lecveo, we have guided that Entresto, Cosentix,
we've guided that Entresto can be a billion-dollar medicine across its indications.
And certainly, we have the aspiration to make Lecveo as big or bigger than Entresto over time.
It's early days, I think, understanding the trajectory of how we get there.
But I would say we see very solid demand for the medicine,
and I think if we could make it in the range of Entresto, that would be a success.
Thank you.
Your next question comes from the line of Simon Baker from Rothschild.
Please go ahead.
Thank you very much for taking my question, and I will stick to the one.
Taking up on your offer, Vaz, could you give us your updated levels of confidence
on the timing and outcome of the Pellicast and Horizon study?
Thanks so much.
Yes, Simon.
So I don't think I have anything new to add, unfortunately,
because we don't have any new information.
But I think we, of course, continue to make sure that the studies,
the studies on track, no change in our expected readout.
We do expect a readout in the early part of the second half of the year.
So no change with respect to that.
I think if we get a positive result overall, that regardless of the relative risk reduction,
we'll find a way to ultimately launch the medicine.
I think what we'll be really looking for is are there either the 90 milligram
pre-specified subgroup or other subgroups where we can really demonstrate a significant benefit
for patients that I think will help with the uptake.
But we have no insight yet as to what would that be.
We've modeled it extensively.
We continue to believe that we've done the right study and are fully powered
for a 20% relative risk reduction in the 70 milligram per DL and higher patient population
and a 25% relative risk reduction in the 90 milligram per DL patient population.
As a reminder, the median level in the study is 108, so we definitely have enrolled